Mark Anthony Gomez

Software Engineer / Front End Developer

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in web development industry. I am skilled in Vue.js, jQuery, Nuxt.js, HTML, CSS, Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET) and C#. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Informatics College.

+63 995 845 7317

gomez.mark29@gmail.com 🤳

Los Banos Laguna, Philippines 🔎

Work Experience

Software Engineer

2017 - PRESENT

JR. Web Developer

2015 - 2017

Software Developer

Lecturer / Instructor

2012 - 2014

Photographer

Freelance

Leandev Inc

Team Lead / Scrum master in small team for Hotel Reservation (Beta) and Project Orange (Prototype)

Deliver minor tasks for API integration (Back-end) for different suppliers

Contact person with multiple suppliers such Priceline, Yrbooking Pro and Yrbooking

Leandev Inc

Front Developer for FlyAkeed (Flight Reservation and Ticketing Application)

Deliver and develop assigned tasks

EHS Philippines

Former: Hoya Manufacturing Philippines Inc.

Handled Production Applications such Barcoding and Evnvelope

printing system, Product Precision Inspection System, etc

Informatics Computer Institute

at Los Banos Laguna

Handled Major and Minor subjects

Assess and perform the programs provided on the cirriculum

PinkShotEyes

Skills

VueJs / NuxtJs / Expressjs Visual Basic.Net / 6.0

Javascript / jQuery

HTML / HTML 5 Java Programming

AJAX MySQL css/css3 PHP

Softwares / Miscellaneous

Visual Studio Code Editor

Source Tree Adobe Photoshop Sublime Microsoft Visual Studio

Jira Microsoft Office

Certifications

National Competency III Visual Graphics

National Competency IV Programming

TM (Teaching Methodology) Plus

International Diploma in Computer Studies (with Credits)

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science

Informatics College Northgate 2011 - 2013

International Advanced Diploma in Computer Studies

Informatics Computer Institute 2008 - 2010

Secondary Education

Trace Computer College 2004 - 2008

github.com/gomezmark

in /in/mark-anthony-gomez-172453141